Peter Poole fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Interviews and transcripts, 1984 - 1986; F-161-2; 10 cm of textual records 68 sound recordings
  - Interviews for Peter Poole's master's thesis, 1986; F-161-2-3; 8 cm of textual records 40 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 55 audio cassettes and 88 .wav files.
    - Garcia, Don, 27 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3523)
      Garcia, Don; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item34.
      - OBJ-3523_SideA.wav
    - Gautier, Roy, 11 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3524)
      Roy Gautier was President, British Columbia and Yukon Building Trades Council, and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Gautier, Roy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item35.
      - OBJ-3524_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3524_SideB.wav
    - Gruntman, Art, 2 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3525)
      Art Gruntman was Vice-President, Canadian Paperworkers' Union; 9th Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Gruntman, Art; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item36.
      - OBJ-3525_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3525_SideB.wav
    - Hansen, Leif, 17 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3526)
      Leif Hansen was Assistant Secretary Manager, Local 212A United Food and Commercial Workers' International Union; 7th Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Hansen, Leif; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item37.
      - OBJ-3526_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3526_SideB.wav
    - Holter, Geoff, 13 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3527)
      Geoff Holter was Chief Representative, Professional Employees Association; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Holter, Geoff; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item38.
      - OBJ-3527_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3527_SideB.wav
    - Keighley, Jef, 8 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3528, Audio cassette OBJ-3529)
      Jef Keighley was Staff Representative, Canadian Association of Mechanical and Allied Workers; and Secretary Treasurer, Lower Mainland Budget Coalition.
      Jef Keighley; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item39, F-161-item40.
      - OBJ-3528_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3528_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3529_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3529_SideB.wav
    - Kelly, Colin, 20 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3530)
      Colin Kelly was President, Local 1, Independent Canadian Transit Workers' Union; and Secretary, Lower Mainland Budget Coalition.
      Kelly, Colin; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item41.
      - OBJ-3530_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3530_SideB.wav
    - Kramer, Mike, 3 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3531)
      Mike Kramer was Secretary Treasurer of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Kramer, Mike; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Interview with Mike Kramer stored on Side A through to 19:11 of Side B of OBJ-3531. See F-161-2-3-0-0-10 for Side B.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item42.
      - OBJ-3531_SideA.wav
    - Kube, Art, 1 April 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3534)
      Art Kube was President, British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee; chief Spokesperson for Operation Solidarity; and Co-chairperson of the Solidarity Coalition.
      Kube, Art; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item45.
      - OBJ-3534_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3534_SideB.wav
    - Kuehn, Larry, 2 September 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3532, Audio cassette OBJ-3533)
      Larry Kuehn was President, British Columbia Teachers' Federation; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Kuehn, Larry; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item43, F-161-item44.
      - OBJ-3532_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3532_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3533_SideA.wav
    - Lavalle, Ed, 1 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3535, Audio cassette OBJ-3536)
      Ed Lavalle was Corresponding Secretary, Lower Mainland Solidarity Coaltion Steering Committee; and table officer, College Institute Educators Association.
      Lavalle, Ed; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item46, F-161-item47.
      - OBJ-3535_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3535_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3536_SideB.wav
    - Lytle, Clive, 8 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-3537, Audio cassette OBJ-3538)
      Clive Lytle was Director of Communications and Education, BC and Yukon Buildings Trade Council; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Lytle, Clive; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item48, F-161-item49.
      - OBJ-3537_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3537_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3538_SideA.wav
    - MacDonald, Bill, 15 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-3539, Audio cassette OBJ-3540)
      Bill MacDonald was President, Hospital Employees Union.
      MacDonald, Bill; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3540 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item50, F-161-item51.
      - OBJ-3539_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3539_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3540_SideA.wav
    - McGrady, Leo, 17 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-3541)
      Leo McGrady was legal counsel for a number of public sector unions.
      McGrady, Leo; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Interview with Leo McGrady recorded on Side A of OBJ-3541.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item52.
      - OBJ-3541_SideA.wav
    - Paton, Nora, 17 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-3542)
      Nora Paton was Chief Executive Officer, BC Nurses Union; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Paton, Nora; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item53.
      - OBJ-3542_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3542_SideB.wav
    - Rice, David, 27 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-26 (Audio cassette OBJ-3543, Audio cassette OBJ-3544)
      David Rice was Director of Research and Legislation (Administrative Director), British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Rice, David; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-3544 only recorded on side B; side A is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item54, F-161-item55.
      - OBJ-3543_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3543_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3544_SideA.wav
    - Roberts, Father Jim, 14 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-27 (Audio cassette OBJ-3545, Audio cassette OBJ-3546)
      Father Jim Roberts was Instructor in Religious Studies, Langara Community College; and Co-chairperson, Solidarity Coalition.
      Roberts, Father Jim; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3546 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item56, F-161-item57.
      - OBJ-3545_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3545_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3546_SideA.wav
    - Ruel, Len, 13 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-28 (Audio cassette OBJ-3547)
      Len Ruel was Director of Organization, Canadian Labour Congress; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Ruel, Len; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item58.
      - OBJ-3547_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3547_SideB.wav
    - Rungren, Cliff, 10 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-29 (Audio cassette OBJ-3548)
      Cliff Rungren was Business Manager and Financial Secretary, Local 213, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Rungren, Cliff; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3548 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item59.
      - OBJ-3548_SideA.wav
    - Rush, Stuart, 14 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-30 (Audio cassette OBJ-3541)
      Stuart Rush was member of the BC Law Union and representative to the Lower Mainland Solidarity Coaltion.
      Rush, Stuart; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Interview with Stuart Rush recorded on Side B of OBJ-3541.
      - OBJ-3541_SideB.wav
    - Shearer, Renate, 28 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-31 (Audio cassette OBJ-3549, Audio cassette OBJ-3550)
      Renate Shearer was Co-chairperson, Provincial Solidarity Coalition, and former Human Rights Commissioner.
      Shearer, Renate; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3550 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item60, F-161-item61.
      - OBJ-3549_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3549_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3550_SideA.wav
    - Shewaga, Stan, 16 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-32 (Audio cassette OBJ-3551)
      Stan Shewaga was President, Local 9, Pulp Paper and Wood Workers of Canada.
      Shewaga, Stan; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item62.
      - OBJ-3551_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3551_SideB.wav
    - Simpson, Shane, 4 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-33 (Audio cassette OBJ-3552)
      Shane Simpson was Representative for the Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition (LMSC) on the Provincial Solidarity Coaltion Steering Committee, and staff worker with LMSC.
      Simpson, Shane; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item63.
      - OBJ-3552_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3552_SideB.wav
    - Smith, Marty, 18 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-34 (Audio cassette OBJ-3560)
      Marty Smith was elected Business Agent, Local 452, Capenters' Union.
      Marty Smith; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Interview starts at the 10 minute mark of OBJ-3560.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item71.
      - OBJ-3560_SideB.wav
    - Steeves, Ralph, 30 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-35 (Audio cassette OBJ-3553)
      Ralph Steeves was President, BC Council of Machinists (International Association of Machinist and Aerospace Workers); 8th Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Steeves, Ralph; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item64.
      - OBJ-3553_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3553_SideB.wav
    - Succamore, Jesse, 2 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-36 (Audio cassette OBJ-3554, Audio cassette OBJ-3555)
      Jesse Succamore was National Secretary Treasurer, Canadian Association of Mechanical and Allied Workers; and 1st Vice-President, Confederation of Canadian Unions.
      Succamore, Jesse; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item65, F-161-item66.
      - OBJ-3554_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3554_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3555_SideA.wav
    - Swanson, Jean, 18 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-37 (Audio cassette OBJ-3556)
      Jean Swanson was Staffperson, Provincial Solidary Coalition.
      Swanson, Jean; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item67.
      - OBJ-3556_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3556_SideB.wav
    - Wasserlein, Frances, 23 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-38 (Audio cassette OBJ-3557)
      Frances Wasserlein was Spokesperson, Women Against the Budget.
      Wasserlein, Frances; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item68.
      - OBJ-3557_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3557_SideB.wav
    - West, Alice, 23 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-39 (Audio cassette OBJ-3558)
      Alice West was Executive Officer, Public Service Alliance of Canada; 10th Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      West, Alice; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item69.
      - OBJ-3558_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3558_SideB.wav
    - Wilson, Fred, 17 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-40 (Audio cassette OBJ-3559, Audio cassette OBJ-3560)
      Fred Wilson was Chairman of the Labour Committee for the Communist Party of Canada (CPC); Provincial Organizational Secretary for CPC; campaign manager for the Committee of Progressive Electors (COPE); and COPE delegate to the Lower Mainland Budget Coaliton (LMCB) and the Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition (LMSC).
      Interview with Fred Wilson recorded on the first 10 minutes of Side A of OBJ-3560.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item70, F-161-item71.
      - OBJ-3559_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3559_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3560_SideA.wav
    - List of tape recorded interviews for Poole Master's thesis, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
    - Personal impressions of the tape recorded interviews and interviewees, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
    - Interview questions directed to Solidarity Coalition and Operation Solidarity, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
    - Transcripts of tape recorded interviews 1/3, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
    - Transcripts of tape recorded interviews 2/3, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
    - Transcripts of tape recorded interviews 3/3, 1986; F-161-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 161-3)